https://www.triangleoshkosh.com/privacy-policy

The store will not work correctly in the case when cookies are disabled.
COVID-19 status : Triangle Manufacturing is operating and is committed to doing our part in supplying parts to our customers. Read more
Menu
BearingsTypeClamshell BearingsFlange BearingsHanger BearingsHVAC Repair KitOffset Flange Mounted BearingsPedestal BearingsPillow Block BearingsSpherical Plain BearingsSpider Blower Bearing Brackets with BearingSplit Pillow Block BearingsTake-Up BearingsMaterialCast - Machined Iron BearingsMolded Nylon BearingsSintered Bronze BearingsSintered Iron BearingsWood Bearings Shaft Size (Bore ID)1/4"5/16"3/8"10 mm7/16"12 mm1/2"13 mm5/8"16 mm3/4"13/16"7/8"15/16"25 mm1"1 1/8"1 3/16"1 1/4"1 3/8"1 1/2"1 3/4"Linkages & Rod EndsTypeLinkage AssembliesSpherical Rod End Bearing Heim JointsThreaded RodsMaterialChrome Plated BearingsSintered Bronze BearingsSintered Iron Bearings Shaft Size (Bore ID)1/4"5/16"8 mm3/8"7/16"16 mmMotor MountsTypeHVAC Repair KitsMotor Mount ArmsMotor Mount BandsSpider Blower Bearing BracketsSpider Blower Bearing Brackets with BearingLazy Susan Bearings Load Capacity (lbs)2003005007501000 Overall Length3"4"6"9"12"Components & MountsTypeFlange Bearing MountsHVAC Repair KitsSet Screw Shaft CollarsMount MaterialSteel Flange Bearing Mounts Shaft Size (Bore ID)5/8"3/4"15/16"1"Product ResourcesBearingsInformational GuidesWhite PapersLinkages & Rod EndsInformational GuidesWhite Papers VideosMotor MountsInformational GuidesLazy Susan BearingsInformational Guides
BearingsTypeClamshell BearingsFlange BearingsHanger BearingsHVAC Repair KitOffset Flange Mounted BearingsPedestal BearingsPillow Block BearingsSpherical Plain BearingsSpider Blower Bearing Brackets with BearingSplit Pillow Block BearingsTake-Up BearingsMaterialCast - Machined Iron BearingsMolded Nylon BearingsSintered Bronze BearingsSintered Iron BearingsWood Bearings Shaft Size (Bore ID)1/4"5/16"3/8"10 mm7/16"12 mm1/2"13 mm5/8"16 mm3/4"13/16"7/8"15/16"25 mm1"1 1/8"1 3/16"1 1/4"1 3/8"1 1/2"1 3/4"Linkages & Rod EndsTypeLinkage AssembliesSpherical Rod End Bearing Heim JointsThreaded RodsMaterialChrome Plated BearingsSintered Bronze BearingsSintered Iron Bearings Shaft Size (Bore ID)1/4"5/16"8 mm3/8"7/16"16 mmMotor MountsTypeHVAC Repair KitsMotor Mount ArmsMotor Mount BandsSpider Blower Bearing BracketsSpider Blower Bearing Brackets with BearingLazy Susan Bearings Load Capacity (lbs)2003005007501000 Overall Length3"4"6"9"12"Components & MountsTypeFlange Bearing MountsHVAC Repair KitsSet Screw Shaft CollarsMount MaterialSteel Flange Bearing Mounts Shaft Size (Bore ID)5/8"3/4"15/16"1"Product ResourcesBearingsInformational GuidesWhite PapersLinkages & Rod EndsInformational GuidesWhite Papers VideosMotor MountsInformational GuidesLazy Susan BearingsInformational Guides
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to Triangle Manufacturing Company and www.TriangleOshkosh.com, and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Triangle include Triangle Manufacturing and www.TriangleOshkosh.com. By using the website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
In order to better provide you with products and services offered on our Site, Triangle may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:
First and Last Name
Mailing Address
E-mail Address
Phone Number
Employer
Job Title
Other personal information you may choose to provide to us via the forms on this Site.
Triangle may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your:
Age
Gender
Race
Other information recorded by website analysis service providers like Google Analytics.
We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) sending us an email message. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Use of your Personal Information
Triangle collects and uses your personal information to operate its website and deliver the services you have requested.
Triangle may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Triangle and its affiliates.
Sharing Information with Third Parties
Triangle does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
Triangle may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Triangle Mfg. and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Triangle may disclose your personal information without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Triangle or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Triangle; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Triangle, or the public.
Triangle Manufacturing may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Triangle manufacturing, in order to determine what Triangle Manufacturing services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Triangle manufacturing to customers whose behaviors indicate that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Tracking User Behavior
Triangle may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Triangle, in order to determine what Triangle services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Triangle to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Automatically collected information
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Triangle. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding the use of the Triangle website.
Use of cookies
The Triangle website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of the cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save your time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned it to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Triangle pages or register with Triangle site or services, a cookie helps Triangle to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Triangle website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the website features that you have customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Triangle services or websites you visit.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statement of any other side and collect personal identifiable information.
Security for your personal information
Triangle secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Triangle uses the following method for this purpose:
SSL Protocol
When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the secure socket layer (SSL) protocol.
We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alterations of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchange between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.
Children under 13
Triangle does not knowingly collect a personal identification information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
Email communications
From time to time, Triangle may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, survey, and/or other general communication. In order to improve our services, we may receive a notification when you open an email from Triangle or click on a link therein.
If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from Triangle manufacturing, you may opt out of such communications by contacting Info@TriangleOshkosh.com.
Changes to this statement
Triangle reserves the right to change this privacy policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the Primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or services available through the site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified privacy policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.
Contact information
Triangle welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Triangle has not adhered to this statement, please contact Triangle Manufacturing at:
Triangle Manufacturing, Inc. 150 Libbey Ave Oshkosh, 64 54901
Email address: info@triangleoshkosh.comTelephone number: 920-235-3710
Effective: October 02, 2019Assistance: Rocket Lawyer
TOTOP
Select and compare up to 4 products.
Compare
Select and compare up to 4 products.
Compare
Privacy Policy
Copyright © Triangle Manufacturing Company. All rights reserved.
